船长要你把船保持在五百尺
Captain wants you to keep 500 feet.
指挥部呼叫驾驶舱 升到五百尺
Maneuvering, Control. Come in shallow to 500 feet.
- 保持五百尺 - 保持五百尺
- Keep 500 feet. - Keep 500 feet, sir.
搞什么鬼?
What the hell's going on, Eddie?
紧急状态 船长请到指挥部
Emergency stations. Captain to the control room.
- 怎么了?  - 5号舱壁关闭
- What's going on? - Number five bulkhead shut down.
- 驾驶舱叫指挥部 - 控制室 我是船长
- Control, Maneuvering. - Control, Captain.
电频率中断了 我要把系统切断
I'm losing electrical frequency. I'll have to break down the system.
测量室呼叫指挥部
Control, Sound Room.
声纳设备丧失动力
Total loss of power on all sonar sets.
浮出水面 全速浮出水面
Surface. Blow forward, blow aft, full ahead.
全速浮出水面 开动探测潜望镜
Full rise on both planes. Raise the search periscope.
天啊
Oh, my God.
把电话接进来
Yeah, put him through.
早安
Good morning, sir.
没有 海军大臣
No, First Sea Lord.
目前还没有漫游者号的消息
There's been no contact with Ranger yet, sir.
看不见它 也没收到危难讯号
No sightings, no distress signals, sir.
好像就是这样
It looks very much like it.
当然 我会的
Yes, of course I will, sir.
我们损失了一艘核潜艇
We've lost one of our nuclear submarines.
(莫斯科)
什么?
What?
波特金号潜艇神秘失踪了
The submarine Potempkin disappeared without trace?
简直是大灾难 主席同志
What a catastrophe, Comrade Chairman.
当然 我会立刻派遣最好的特工
Yes, of course. I'll assign our best agent immediately.
- 鲁贝威区 特工3X在哪? - 在休假
- Rubelvitch, where is Agent XXX? - On leave, General.
在人民休养康复中心
At a people's rest and recuperation center.
这个周未真愉快
It's been a wonderful weekend.
- 我永远不会忘记 - 我也是
- I shall never forget it. - Nor will I.
我们何时会再见面?
When can we meet again?
等到我的任务完成后即可
As soon as my mission is accomplished.
我要是了 我今晚要到达奥地利
I must go. I have to be in Austria tonight.
再躺五分钟吧
Five more minutes.
3X,呼叫3X
Agent XXX. Calling Agent XXX.
请你马上到总部报到
You will report to headquarters immediately.
3X 请答话
Agent XXX, acknowledge and verify.
我是3X 讯息收到 明白
This is XXX. Message received and understood.
是的 首相大人 我明白事态的严重性
Yes, Mr. Prime Minister. I understand the gravity of the situation.
我会马上调遣最好的特工出动
Yes, I'll put our best man on it at once.
再见
Good-bye.
钱班儿?007在哪?
Moneypenny, where is 007?
他在奥地利执行任务
He's on a mission, sir, in Austria.
叫他立刻撤出
Tell him to pull out, immediately.
詹姆斯 我找不到语言去形容
Oh, James, I cannot find the words.
我帮你找一个适合的词语吧
Let me try and enlarge your vocabulary.
(007马上向总部报到)
怎么了?
What's happened?
- 你要到哪去? - 对不起 出了事情了
- Where are you going? - Sorry, darling. Something came up.
可是我需要你
But, James, I need you.
英国也是
So does England.
他刚刚离开
He has just left.
通话完毕
Over and out.
收到了 我们在等他 通话完毕
Message received. We are waiting. Over and out.
去吧
Now.
《007系列之海底城》
叫3X进来
Send in Agent XXX.
将军同志 你找我?
You sent for me, Comrade General.
早安 阿玛索娃少校 我们正面对一个棘手的局面
Good morning. Major Amasova, we are facing a most delicate situation.
我们的核潜艇完全失踪了
Our nuclear submarine Potempkin has disappeared.
被破坏了
Sabotage?
这就有待你去调查 我们有一个线索
That is for you to find out. We have one lead:
在开罗有个联络人
A connection in Cairo.
今晚出发
You leave tonight.
没有别的事情了吧?
Will that be all?
还有一件事
There is one more thing.
很遗憾 特工西凯尔波索夫殉职了
I regret to inform you, Major, that Agent Sergei Borzov has been killed.
他在奥地利阿雨卑斯山的伯加顿执行任务时遇害
On a mission at Berngarten in the Austrian Alps.
真是不幸的事件 将军同志
A tragic occurrence, Comrade General.
我们知道你跟波索夫
It had not escaped our notice that you and Agent Borzov...
并不只是朋友的关系
had been more than friends for some time.
我很难过
I'm very sorry.
他时怎样死的?
How did he die?
详细情况还不知道
We haven't all the details yet.
应该是跟英国的情报组织有关
It appears he'd become involved in a British Secret Service operation.
如有任何消息 请你通知我
Please keep me informed, Comrade General.
我很希望跟那个…
I should very much like to meet...
把他杀死的人见面
whoever was responsible for his death.
- 早安 - 早安
- Good morning, sir. - Good morning.
- 早安 007 - 你好 Q
- Good morning, 007. - Hello, Q.
- 任务成功吗 - 马马虎虎吧
- Mission successful? - On and off.
- 早安 中校 - 早安
- Good morning, Commander. - Good morning, sir.
- 福斯夫上校 - 你好
- Captain Forsyth. - Sir.
他是邦德中校
Commander Bond, sir.
- 国访部长佛雷克葛瑞 - 早安中校
- Mr. Fredrick Gray, Minister of Defense. - Good morning, Commander.
潜艇舰队同令哈尔盖里夫上将
Admiral Hargreaves, Flag Officer, Submarines.
- 是皇家方舟号吧 - 对
- Ark Royal, wasn't it? - Yes, sir.
- M把情况告诉你了吧? - 是的
- I believe M told you about this. - Yes, Minister.
请各位到这边来
Over here, please, gentlemen.
(位置  路线)
这是漫游者号预定的巡航范围
This, I take it, is Ranger's prearranged coastal patrol area.
- 嗯 - 有多少人知道这条路线?
- That's right. - How many people knew this course?
哈尔盖里夫上将 我…
Admiral Hargreaves, myself...
还有潜艇的船长泰博特
and Talbot, the submarine captain.
天啊
Good God.
这是从什么地方得来的?
Where did this come from?
对不起 这是目前的高度机密
I'm sorry, Benson. For the moment, that's top secret.
我明白了 这条追踪路线表示…
I see, sir. Commander, this tracing means...
苏联人可以追踪水中的棱子潜艇 并把它击沉
that the Russians can track our nuclear submarines underwater and sink them.
- 我相信他们已经做到了 - 怎么做到的?这是不可能的
- I believe it does. - How could they? It's impossible.
其实很简单
It's quite simple.
最可能的是热能识别法
Heat signature recognition, most likely.
- 我可以解释吗 - 当然可以
- With your permission, Minister? - Yes, of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
装有红外线热能感应器的卫星…
We already know that satellites with infrared heat sensors...
可以凭着导弹尾部的火光追踪导弹的位置
can detect a nuclear missile in flight by its tail fire.
那又如何?
Well?
有人可以探测潜艇的尾波
Someone can now locate a submerged nuclear submarine...
以确定潜艇的位置
in exactly the same way, by its wake.
也就是说 他们可以暗中破坏西方的防卫战略
That means they can totally undermine our Western defense strategy.
好像是这样
Yes, it looks like it.
这份系统图是从哪里来的?
Where did we get that tracing, Freddie?
从开罗寄来的外交信袋
Cairo, diplomatic bag.
有人想出售追踪系统图
Somebody got the plans of that tracking system and is trying to sell them.
他们把路线图送来证明系统是真的
They sent us that tracing as proof that it's genuine.
若要跟他交易 价钱将会很昂贵
Then, if there is a deal to be made, the price will be high.
高昂? 历直是天文数字
"High?" Astronomical.
失踪了的潜艇装有十六枚导弹
That missing submarine had 16 Polaris missiles aboard.
我们在埃及有联络人吗?
We have a contact in Egypt?
M会把详情告诉你 你今晚出发
M will give you the details. You leave tonight.
巴哈曼博士 马柯堆兹教授
Dr. Bechmann and Professor Markovitz.
谢谢
Thank you.
是该跟两位道别的时候了
Gentlemen, now that the moment has come to bid you farewell...
我恭喜你们两位
I congratulate both you, Doctor, and you, Professor...
凭着你们的努力
on your brilliant work in the development...
成功开发出潜艇追踪系统
of the submarine tracking system.
在你们的努力下 我很高兴的说
Thanks primarily to you, I'm happy to say...
行动的第一阶段
that the first phase of our operation...
获得重大成功
has met with considerable success.
我已经吩咐助手...
I have instructed my assistant...
在你们的...
to have paid into your...
瑞士银行户口
Swiss bank account...
分别存入一千万美元
the sum of $10 million each.
- 谢谢 - 非常谢谢你
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, indeed.
我们的合作就到此为止
And that, I think, concludes our business.
不过 在你们离开之前
Before you go, however...
我很遗憾要告诉你们…
I very much regret to inform you...
我发觉事情
that a dangerous development...
出现了危险的变故
has recently been brought to my notice.
有人尝试把追踪系统计划
Someone has been attempting to sell the plans...
出售给…
of our tracking project...
我们敌对的强国
to competing world powers.
那个人跟这个计划的关系密切
Someone intimately associated with the project.
亲爱的 请你先行离开
My dear, it would be more seemly if you left us.
谢谢
Thank you.
你背叛了我
It was you who betrayed me.
你取得了所有的资料
You had access to all the information.
现在你要接受惩罚
Now you will pay the penalty.
我再次致以衷心的感激
Once again, gentlemen, my most profound thanks.
- 山多尔 - 是的
- Sandor. - Yes, sir.
大钢牙
Jaws.
我派你去
I'm assigning you the task...
找回追踪系统的...
of recovering the microfilm copy...
微缩影片拷贝
of the tracking system.
山多尔 你跟他一起去 服从他
Sandor, you will go with him. Obey him.
把所有曾经接独过微缩影片的人
Every person who even comes into contact with that microfilm...
统统都干掉
is to be eliminated.
直升机准备起飞
Stand by for helicopter takeoff.
所有人员离开飞行甲板
All personnel, clear the flight deck platform.
把二千万元的转帐取消
Cancel transfer of $20 million.
知会马柯堆兹教授...
Inform next of kin that a tragic accident...
和巴哈曼博士的亲属
has resulted in the death of Professor Markovitz...
他们不幸遇难
and Dr. Bechmann.
并已进行海葬
The funeral was at sea.
愿真主赐福给这个堂皇的住宅
May the peace of Allah descend upon this magnificent abode...
并容许我这个孤苦的旅客进入
and allow a poor traveler to enter.
但愿这个粗劣的地方
May the hospitality of these miserable quarters...
能够满足你那尊贵的需求
be sufficient to your honored needs.
詹姆斯.邦德 多年不见  很高兴再见到你!
James Bond, what a delightful surprise after all these years.
- 请坐 - 谢谢
- Sit down. - Thank you.
我一直在纳闷 你离开剑桥后改究竟在干什么?
I always wondered what you were gonna do when you went down from Cambridge.
我从来都知道你想要做什么 胡笙
I never had any problems knowing what you were going to do, Hosein.
我们不是只有石油而已
We don't only have oil, you know.
你想要什么?羊的眼睛?枣子?
What can I offer you? Sheep's eyes? Dates?
- 这是伏特加马丁尼? - 情报资料
- Vodka martini? - Information.
是谁要出售潜艇追踪系统?
Who is putting the submarine tracking system on the market?
你在商业上这么有毅力 还真可惜
What a pity it is you insist on being so businesslike.
最终会跟你交手的那个人…
The gentleman you will eventually be dealing with...
叫马斯卡巴
is a certain Max Kalba.
- 最终?  - 要接触卡巴
- "Eventually?" - To reach Kalba...
你得跟一个叫菲克治的人联络
you must first make contact with a man called Fekkesh.
我把他在开罗的地做给你吧
Aziz Fekkesh. I'll give you his apartment address in Cairo.
今天已太晚去见他
It's too late to meet him today.
你晚上愿意留宿在这吗?
Can I persuade you to accept a bed for the night?
谢谢你 不过…我觉得...
That's kind of you, Hosein, but I really feel I...
你真的不要在这里留宿吗?
Are you quite sure I can't persuade you to stay the night?
当一个人来到埃及时
When one is in Egypt...
很应该好好地挖掘当地的宝藏
one should delve deeply into its treasures.
我就是 对不起 大门是开的
Yes. Oh, I'm sorry. The door was open.
我在电话上跟菲克治先生约好了
Mr. Fekkesh is expecting me. I phoned him.
他叫我带个讯息给你
He asked me to give you a message.
他晚一点才有空
He will be late.
请问他在哪?
May I ask where he is?
他吩咐我在你等待时 要好好的招待你
Mr. Fekkesh asked me to entertain you while you are waiting.
真的吗?
Really?
菲克治在哪?
Where is Fekkesh?
你的疑心很重
You are very suspicious.
我觉得我这样会活得更久
I find I live much longer that way.
他在哪
Now where is he?
如果你有任何需要的话
If there's anything at all you would like...
我已生吃过了中饭 可是…
I had lunch, but I seem to have missed dessert.
虽然我急欲跟他会面 但也不想他突然出现  打扰我们
As urgent as my appointment is, I'd hate him to walk in and surprise us.
不会的
There is no danger of that.
他不会这么快来到吧?
He'll be some time then?
他还有别的约会吗?
Is he meeting someone?
对不起 我不可以回答你
I'm sorry, I cannot answer that question.
你可以的
Oh, I think you can.
菲克治在哪?
Where's Fekkesh?
全字塔
Pyramids.
他对我真是有帮助
What a helpful chap.
今天晚上 你来到了全球…
You have come tonight to the most fabulous...
最迷人和著名的地方
and celebrated place in the world.
在吉萨高原上 永恒地耸立着
Here on the Plateau of Giza stands forever...
人类最伟大的成就
the mightiest of human achievements.
所有曾踩踏过这片黄沙的…
No traveler, emperor, merchant or poet...
旅客、帝王、商人和诗人
has trodden on these sands...
对之无不肃然起敬
and not gasped in awe.
夜幕随之升起
The curtain of night is about to rise...
舞台上即将要上演
and disclose the stage on which...
一个文明国度的戏剧
the drama of a civilization took place.
当中的东西自盘古初开已经存在
Those involved have been present since the dawn of history...
顽强地跟风沙对抗
pitched stubbornly against sand and wind.
沙漠的声音
And the voice of the desert...
连续多个世纪
has crossed the centuries.
失陪一会 我马上回来
Excuse me, Major. I'll be back in a moment.
每个黎明 我看着旭日
With each new dawn, I see the sun god rise...
在尼罗河岸东升
on the far bank of the Nile.
我是他那忠心的看守人
I am the faithful warden at the foot of his lord.
我既忠心 又有警觉性
So faithful, so vigilant...
跟他非常靠近
so near him...
他向我显现
that he gave me his face for my own.
我是法老的同伴
I am a pharaoh's companion...
我就是他 法老王
and I am he, the pharaoh.
这是四千五百年前
This is the tomb of Cheops...
第四王朝的基奥普斯王的陵墓
Pharaoh of the Fourth Dynasty 4,500 years ago.
他建了这座全字塔
Here is the Great Pyramid which he built...
保护自己 跟死神对抗
to defend himself against death.
在陵墓深处
Here in the depths of his tomb...
皇帝的仆人正等待着被召唤
a servant of the king awaits the call...
以展开迈向永恒之旅
to set out upon his journey into eternity.
死神在等待看
Death lies waiting.
(马斯卡巴 穆杰巴俱乐部 晚上九时四十分)
菲克治在哪?
Where is Fekkesh?
跟法老在一起
With the pharaohs.
- 你杀了他 - 不 我发现他时 他已经死了
- You killed him. - No, he was dead when I found him.
希望你喜欢这场秀
Hope you enjoyed the show.
晚安
Good night.
我真是喜出望外 欢迎来到穆杰巴俱乐部
What an unexpected pleasure. Welcome to the Mujaba Club.
要喝一杯吗? 阿玛索娃少校
Buy you a drink, Major Amasova?
还是我该称呼你做3X?
Or may I call you XXX?
你知道我是谁?
You know who I am.
你让人留下深刻印象
You made quite an impression.
我替我的手下道歉
I'm sorry about Ivan and Boris.
他们做得过火了
They exceeded their orders.
好员工难求
Good staff is hard to find these days.
你要什么?
Yes, sir?
请给这位小姐一杯巴卡第加冰块
The lady will have a Bacardi on the rocks.
这位先生要伏特加马丁尼 要摇而不要搅的
For the gentleman, vodka martini, shaken not stirred.
说得对
Touche.
詹姆斯.邦德海军中校
Commander James Bond.
被选中加入了英国情报组织
Recruited to the British Secret Service from the Royal Navy.
可以合法杀人 杀人无数
Licensed to kill, and has done so on numerous occasions.
拥有无数女朋友 曾结过一次婚
Many lady friends, but married only once.
- 妻子被杀... - 好了 我知道你很了解我
- Wife killed... - All right, you've made your point.
你很敏感
You're sensitive.
对某些事确很敏感
About certain things, yes.
请恕我失陪
Now, if you'll excuse me.
很可惜 我已经有约会
Tragically, I have a previous engagement.
幸好我也是
Happily enough, so do I.
- 告辞了 邦德先生 - 应该说再见
- Good-bye, Mr. Bond. - Let's say au revoir.
我有个很奇怪的预感 我们会再见的
I have the oddest feeling we'll be meeting again sometime.
我找卡巴先生
I'm looking for Mr. Kalba.
卡巴先生是这个俱乐部的老板
Mr. Max Kalba is the owner of the club, sir.
他在那里
Over there.
卡巴先生? 我叫詹姆斯 邦德
Mr. Kalba, my name is James Bond.
怎么了
What of it?
你跟菲克治先生有约会
You had an appointment with Mr. Fekkesh.
- 那又如何? - 他不能来了
- Well? - He won't be joining you.
你有一些我想买的东西 等一下
You have something I'm interested in buying.
我对那东西也有兴趣竞投
Just a moment. I would like to bid for it too.
你忘了拿饮品
You forgot your drink.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来你有对手了 邦德先生
It seems you have competition, Mr. Bond.
在我看来
From where I sit...
你也看得出来她的身段一流
I fancy you will find the lady's figure hard to match.
号争者可以看看那件东西吗?
Might the contestants be permitted to view the article for sale?
谁要先喊价?
Well, now, who will start the bidding?
卡巴先生 有电话找你 是紧急电话
Mr. Kalba, sir, the telephone. An urgent call.
失陪
Excuse me.
借光
Pardon me.
我是卡巴 请问是谁?
This is Kalba. Hello?
要再来一杯吗?
Another?
(暂停使用)
我们不能再用这种方式见面了
We've really got to stop meeting like this.
卡巴去接电话了 他怎么了?
Kalba was called to the phone. What happened?
他被打断…永久地打断了
He was cut off, permanently.
那卷微缩影片呢?
Where is the microfilm?
你可以搜身
Search me.
一定是给他拿走了 否则你不会在这里的
He must have it, or you wouldn't be here.
你不知道他的来历
You don't know who he is.
- 他是职业杀手 - 外号大钢牙?
- He's a professional killer. - Called Jaws?
你听好
Make no mistake, Mr. Bond...
那卷微缩影片...
I want that microfilm...
我是要定的了
and I'm going to get it.
除非是我先得手
Unless I get it first.
小心
Watch out!
别动
Don't move.
微缩影片
Give me the microfilm.
埃及的建筑商
Egyptian builders.
对不起 你迟了一步了
Sorry. You're just too late.
钥匙给我
Give me the key!
钥匙
The key!
试用大钥匙
Try the big one.
它可以弹别的音调吗?
Can you play any other tune?
让我们试倒裆 就是向后退
Let's try reverse. That's backwards.
让我来开车好吗?
Would you like me to drive?
女人驾驶
Women drivers.
闭嘴 你看着
Quiet. Watch this.
是摇而不是搅的
Shaken, but not stirred.
一定是铆工 替这头大猩猩镶的牙
That gorilla must have his teeth fixed by a riveter.
谢谢你刚才弃我而去
By the way, thanks for deserting me back there.
女人都得为自己打算 记得吗?
Every woman for herself. Remember?
不过你依然救了我一命
Still, you did save my life.
圣人都会犯错
We all make mistakes, Mr. Bond.
气缸盖的密封垫
The cylinder head gasket.
他说什么?
What did he say?
他觉得我们穿得过分隆重了  不过他会送我们去开罗
He thinks we're overdressed, but he'll take us to Cairo.
好极了
Good.
越来越冷了
It's getting cold.
我要怎么做才能使你暖一点?
Is there anything I can do to warm you up?
你不必担心我
You don't have to worry about me.
我在西伯利亚曾经上过求生课程
I went on a survival course in Siberia.
我相信你们很多同胞也修过
Yes, I believe a great number of your countrymen do.
他们教你什么?
What did they teach you?
拥有积极的斗志是非常重要的
That it's very important to have a positive mental attitude.
没有更实际一点的吗?
Nothing more practical than that?
食物也是非常重要的
Food is also very important.
这有呢?
What else?
在有需要的时候互相取暖
When necessary, shared bodily warmth.
我喜欢这个
That's the part I like.
他们在西伯利亚真的是这么做的吗?
Is this really what they do in Siberia?
是 不过做法不同
Yes, but not how they do it.
你不是想占我的便宜 对吗
You're not trying to take advantage of me, are you?
我从没这样想过
The thought never crossed my mind.
就当事情越来越有意思的时候
Just when it was getting interesting.
那个女孩在哪?
Where's the girl?
- 早安 钱班儿 - 早安 詹姆斯
- Morning, Moneypenny. - Good morning, James.
他在里面吗
Is he in?
一定是个很热闹派对
It must have been quite a party.
闷死人 钱班儿
Boring.
事实上 我睡着了
I dropped off.
你好 我们正在等你
Hello, James. We've been expecting you.
早安
Good morning, sir.
计划有变
There's been a change in plan.
你也许已经认出了他是国安会的戈高尔将军
You probably recognize my opposite number in the KGB, General Gogol.
我相信你跟阿玛索娃少校很熟
I believe you're familiar with Major Amasova.
只知道她抽哪个品牌的香烟
Enough to know which brand of cigarette she smokes.
对方政府都同意投资资源
Our respective governments...
以协助我们找出潜艇的下落
agreed to pool their resources to find out what happened to our submarines.
我们踏入了
We have entered a new era...
英苏合作的新纪元
of Anglo-Soviet cooperation.
为了显示饿国的诚意
As a sign of Russian good faith...
我准备交出由3X找到的
I'm prepared to make available to you the microfilm...
微缩影片
recovered by Agent XXX.
可以说是不费吹灰之力
With considerable ease, I might add.
别费心了 这东西一点用都没有
Don't bother. It's useless.
我在船上检查过了
I examined it on the boat.
我可以保证它是真的
I assure you it is quite genuine.
只是最重要的技术资料已经被拿走了
Except that the vital technical information has been taken out.
这东西只是用来吊我们的胃口
This was only intended to whet our appetites.
也许Q会有所发现
Maybe Q can make something out of it.
我要那在在茶会前准备好
I want that ready for Akmid's tea party.
你先走
After you, Alexis.
- 不 你先走 - 谢谢
- After you, Miles. - Thank you.
那可使你掉眼泪
That could bring tears to your eyes.
大家准备好了没有?
Everybody ready? Right.
我们确定这些图像是在意大利起草的
We're pretty certain that this drawing was drafted in Italy.
纸张是威尼斯制的八开纸
The size corresponds with a Venetian octavo...
字样是意大利文
and the typeface is an Italian one.
截线上有一条轻微的痕迹
Now, note the slight upward stress on the transversals.
那是什么标记
What's that mark there?
应该放在...
Probably a show-through of something...
草图下面的纸张
the drawing was resting on when it was photographed.
一定是匆忙拍下的
Must have been done in a hurry.
- 可以把它放大吗? - 等一下
- Can you enlarge it? - Wait a minute.
(小礼拜堂)
- "小礼拜堂"是什么意思? - 即是礼拜堂
- "Oratory?" What is that? - It's another word for chapel.
看来像是主教的冠冕
Looks a bit like a bishop's mitre.
那是一条鱼
It is a fish.
是斯特龙伯格航运的标志
That is the symbol of the Stromberg Shipping Line.
世界超级富豪之一的卡尔斯特龙伯格?
Karl Stromberg? He's one of the richest men in the world.
是西方主要的资本主义剥削者之一
One of the principle capitalist exploiters of the West, sir.
那不是"礼拜堂"而是"实验室"
So it's not "oratory," it's laboratory.
斯特龙伯格拥有海洋研究实验室
Stromberg has a marine research laboratory.
应该是在科西嘉
On Corsica, I believe.
非常好
Well done.
其实那是在萨丁尼亚岛
Actually, it is in Sardinia.
真聪明
That's brilliant.
我相信这两位能干的人
I'm certain that two such perceptive talents...
会喜欢一起到萨丁尼亚岛工作
will enjoy working together in Sardinia...
实践英苏合作的梦想
and that it will help to make Anglo-Soviet cooperation a reality.
是这里了
Here we are.
晚餐非常美味 谢谢
That was a delicious meal. Thank you.
我不知道原来你的胃口是这么大的
I didn't realize you had such a healthy appetite.
我也不知道
Neither did I.
一定是搭火车的关系吧 我很喜欢搭火车
It must be traveling by train. I always enjoy it.
我记得有一次...
I remember when...
你记起了什么呢?
What do you remember?
我几乎要谈到一趟任务了
I was going to talk about a mission.
很可笑吧?
Silly, isn't it?
我们是同行 却不能交谈
We can't talk, and yet we're in the same business.
- 而且还处于敌对的阵营 - 现在我们并不是敌人
- But with rival companies. - We're not rivals at the moment.
你有兴趣在睡前跟我喝一杯吗?
Then how about a nightcap, on the company?
我的客人
My company.
对不起 我有预感明天将会很忙
I'm very sorry. I have an idea tomorrow is going to be a busy day.
- 我必须要睡觉 - 嗯
- I must sleep. - Yes.
- 好吧 好好睡 - 你也是
- Well, then, sleep well. - And you.
晚安
Good night.
怎么了?
What happened?
他走进来要吃东西
He just dropped in for a quick bite.
你受伤了
You're hurt.
待会再处理它
Later.
让我先照顾你
Let's worry about you.
他们在求生训练上如何教你的?
What was it they taught you on that survival course?
要有积极的斗志
A positive mental attitude.
互相取暖
And shared bodily warmth.
没说过要怎么避风吗?
Nothing about keeping out of drafts?
你仍然喜欢搭火车吗?
Still enjoy traveling by train?
你救了我一命
You saved my life.
谢谢你 詹姆斯
Thank you, James.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你为什么不先躺下让我看看?
Why don't you lie down and let me look at it?
绷带要怎么用?
What can we use for a bandage?
这样如何?
How about this?
等等
Wait a moment.
- 早安 少校 - 早安
- Good morning, Major Boothroyd. - Good morning, Major.
看看Q带了什么给我们 很不错吧了
Look what Q has brought for us. Isn't it nice?
你留踪听好 007
Right. Now pay attention, 007.
你小踪使用它 它有特殊装置
Take great care of this equipment. There are some special accessories...
- 我有试过让你失望吗了 - 经常都会
- Have I ever let you down? - Frequently.
我们预订了房间的 我们姓斯特林
You have a reservation for me. The name is Sterling.
对 斯特林伉俪 在开罗预订的
Yes. Mr. And Mrs. Sterling. Booked from Cairo.
对
That's right.
我们预留了A5套房 里面包括客厅 和两间卧房
We have Suite A-5 for you; a sitting room and two bedrooms.
钱班儿真是过分有效率了 我有留言吗?
Moneypenny being over-efficient. Do you have any messages for me?
谢谢
Thank you.
太好了 他愿意正式接见我们
Excellent. We have been granted an audience.
- 斯特林先生 - 是的
- Mr. Sterling? - Yes.
我叫娜欧蜜 斯特龙伯格先生派我来的
I'm Naomi. Mr. Stromberg sent me to collect you.
你好吗? 她是内子…
How do you do? This is my wife...
也是我的助年
who also happens to be my assistant.
- 你是来度假的吗 - 只要是有海洋的地方
- You are on holiday here? - Where there's an ocean...
海洋生物学家就无法休息
a marine biologist is never on holiday.
我们可以先请你喝一杯吗?
Can we offer you a drink before we go?
不 谢了 斯特龙伯格先生是非常忙碌的
No, thank you. Mr. Stromberg's a very busy man.
他的时间很宝贵
His time is precious.
真漂亮的造物
What a handsome craft.
线条一流
Such lovely lines.
谢谢
Thank you.
真是令人钦佩
Very impressive.
我跟斯特龙伯格先生见面时...
I wonder if you'd mind showing my wife around...
- 你可以带我妻子游览一下吗? - 好的
- while I'm with Mr. Stromberg. - Of course.
- 还边走 - 谢谢
- This way. - Thank you.
别替娜欧蜜添麻烦 亲爱的
Don't be a bother to Naomi, darling.
- 我为上回来 - 还有一件事...
- I'll be back soon. - By the way...
先生不太喜欢握年的
Mr. Stromberg prefers not to shake hands.
- 请按第三个按钮 - 谢谢
- It's the third button. - Thank you.
当地球还有恕成的地方…
Why do we seek to conquer space...
有待发掘时 为何还要征服太空
when seven-tenths of our universe remains to be explored?
海底世界
The world beneath the sea.
你看来已经准备就绪 要修正还个错处
You seem to be well-equipped to repair that oversight.
我叫劳勃斯特林 非常感谢你接见我
My name is Robert Sterling. It's very kind of you to receive me.
我很乐意跟志同道合的人见面
It's always a pleasure to welcome someone with a mutual interest.
还里有数目繁多的珍贵品种
An extraordinary number of rare species.
你当然可以分辨那是什么吧
You recognize that variety, of course.
当然
Of course.
有翅飞鱼
Other fish avoid it.
其他鱼类对他都敬而远之 背上的刺充满毒液
Those dorsal spines are laden with venom.
很漂亮 却是从以致命的
Handsome, but deadly.
你果然是这方面的专家
I see you know your subject.
成功在于尝试
One tries.
你的家非常华丽壮观
You have a remarkable establishment here.
我喜欢遁世
I'm somewhat of a recluse.
我希望可以用我喜欢的形式生活
I wish to conduct my life on my own terms...
住在我认同的环境里
and in surroundings with which I can identify.
这就是有钱人的特权
That is a privilege of wealth.
你不怀念外面的世界吗?
Don't you miss the outside world?
对我来说 还里就是全世界
For me, this is all the world.
有美好的一面
There's beauty...
也有丑陋的一面
there's ugliness...
还有死亡
and there is death.
你一定会对这个很感兴趣
I think you will find this interesting.
海底城
An underwater city.
很迷人 不是吗
Fascinating, isn't it?
这是人类未来的唯一希望
The only hope for the future of mankind.
大家都有梦想
We all have our dreams.
不是梦想 斯特林先生很快就会成真
No dream, Mr. Sterling. Soon a reality.
请恕我失陪 我还要处理事务
I'm afraid you must excuse me. I have business to attend to.
再见 斯特林先生
Good-bye.
假如我们不会再见 我祝福你的研究顺利
If we don't meet again, I wish you luck with your research.
谢谢 今天的惊鸿一瞥
Thank you. The brief glimpse you've afforded me today...
只会激励我更用踪研究
will only encourage me to redouble my efforts.
再见
Good-bye.
- 真有趣 - 你在这里
- How interesting. - There you are.
你得看看这个模型 真漂亮
Darling, you should look at this model. It's beautiful.
这是本公司船队的最新成员
This is the Liparus...
利帕鲁斯号
the latest addition to the Stromberg fleet.
九个月前才下水的
Launched nine months ago.
它重逾一百万吨 是世上最大的油轮
At over a million tons, it's the largest tanker in the world.
- 还是比不上马克斯号 - 真的吗了?
- After the Karl Marx, of course. - Really, darling?
你的见识真是广博
It's amazing the items of information you store away.
他们就是火车上的人吗
Were they the two on the train?
詹姆斯.邦德
James Bond...
女的是俄国特工阿玛索娃少校
and the woman is Major Amasova, a Russian agent.
让他们走到岸边
Let them get ashore...
然后把他们干掉
and then kill them.
你怎么神秘亏亏的? 我们要到哪去?
You're being very secretive. Where are we going?
我想再看一下那个实验室
I want another look at that Stromberg laboratory.
你可以从那儿操纵追踪系统吗?
Do you think you could operate the tracking system from there?
有可能的
It's possible.
我们只知道那两艘核潜艇失踪了
All we know for sure is that two nuclear submarines are missing.
你觉得那艘油轮的模型怎么样
What did you think of that tanker model?
船头的设计有点古怪
There was something strange about the design of her bows.
我已要求M去调查一下
I've asked M to check her out.
- 詹姆斯 那辆机车... - 已经跟踪了我们一英里多了
- James, that motorcycle... - Has been following us for a mile.
虽然它有羽饰 始终不能飞
All those feathers and he still can't fly.
我知道 你不用说
Yes, I know. Don't tell me.
你曾否感觉过有人不喜欢你?
You ever get the feeling somebody doesn't like you?
你会游泳吗?
Can you swim?
是该向不速之客道别的时候了
It's time we said good-bye to an uninvited guest.
终于没有人骚扰我们了
Alone at last.
我们就是要看还个
That's what we've come to see.
扶稳
Brace yourself.
你看!
Look!
你怎么会知道的?
How did you know about that?
两年前 我偷了这辆车子的蓝图
I stole the blueprints of this car two years ago.
我们会没事吗?
Do you think we can make it?
你好
Hello.
- 我有个留言要给你 - 你刚刚已经传送过了
- I have a message for you. - I think you just delivered it.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉打扰你了...
Sorry to interrupt you...
我要M替我调查…
but I asked M for a list of all the ports...
那艘油轮停泊的港口
the Stromberg tanker had called at.
答案如何
What is the answer?
她自建成以来
In the nine months since she was fitted out...
从没停泊的记绿
there is no record of her having put into port anywhere.
若是真的话 那就很奇怪了
That's very odd, if it's true.
在这方面 我们不会弄错的
We don't make mistakes of that sort.
你的口气很像俄国人
You sound just like a Russian.
我们应该仔细检查那艘油轮 你觉得呢了
I think we should take a closer look at that tanker, don't you?
对
Yes, I do.
我应该联络戈高尔吗?
Shall I contact Gogol?
没这个需要
There's no need.
- M已经通知了他 - 很漂亮
- M has already offered to fix it. - Very nice.
我在奥地利伯加顿买的
It's Austrian. I bought it in Berngarten.
- 当时我在滑雪 - 什么时候
- I was doing some skiing. - When was this?
大概三个星期 干吗?
About three weeks ago. Why?
你认得他吗?
Do you recognize him?
他是谁?
Who is he?
我爱的人
The man I loved.
三周前他在伯加顿
He was in Berngarten three weeks ago.
你是否杀了他?
Did you kill him?
当有人要在你身后...
When someone's behind you on skis at 40 miles an hour...
边杀你的时候...
trying to put a bullet in your back...
你不会有时间去记住他的客貌
you don't always have time to remember a face.
在我们这行 总会有人被杀
In our business, people get killed.
我们都知道 他也一样
We both know that. So did he.
不是他死 便是我亡
It was either him or me.
问题的答案是: 是的 我杀了他
The answer to the question is yes. I did kill him.
那么 当任务完成之后
Then, when this mission is over...
我会杀了你
I will kill you.
进来
Come in.
- 卡特司令官?  - 我就是 欢迎你
- Commander Carter? - That's right. Welcome aboard.
少校 请坐 你要喝点什么吗?
Major. Have a seat. Can I get you something?
不 谢了 不知道少校要不要
Not for me, thank you. I don't know about the major.
对不起 我没想到你是女人
I'm sorry. I hadn't expected you to be a woman.
我是俄军的阿玛索娃少校
Aboard this vessel, Commander, I am Major Amasova of the Russian Army.
- 对 - 谢谢你出手相助
- Yeah, sure. - It's good of you to help us out.
我已经为你们准备了两个客舱
Got a couple cabins at your disposal.
谢谢
Thank you.
少校 欢迎你使用我的浴室
Major, you're most welcome to use the shower in my quarters.
你不用特别优待我的
You do not have to show me any special favors, Commander.
我只觉得这样做比较好
All the same, I think it might be better if I did.
是太平洋的潜艇传过来的
From Com Sub Atlantic, sir.
好
Right.
怎么了?
What's the matter, sailor?
没见过少校洗澡吗
You never see a major taking a shower before?
(尼帕鲁斯号)
准备再次观察目标
Stand by for second observation on target.
启动潜望镜
Up scope.
停
Check.
目标方向及距离已记下
Target bearing. Mark. Range. Mark.
放下潜望镜
Down scope.
- 一个师团 - 距离六千二百码
- One division in high power. - Range 6,200 yards, sir.
船头的角度五十
Angle on the bow, port 50.
控制室、鱼雷室 登艇部队已准备好
Control, Torpedo Room. Boarding party ready, sir.
船长 最佳的方法是120时速三海里
Captain, sir, our best solution for the target is 120. Speed three knots.
甲板 向北面转 驾驶舱 加速至11海里
Officer of the deck, come right north. Maneuvering, make turns for 11 knots.
甲板船员收到
Officer of the deck, aye, sir.
哪颗子弹有我的名字?  第一颗还是最后一颗?
Which bullet has my name on it? The first or the last?
我从没失败试过任何任务
I have never failed on a mission, Commander. Any mission.
这样的话
In that case, Major...
我们之间必然有一方会很失望
one of us is bound to end up gravely disappointed...
无论是…
because neither of the...
指挥部 电频率中断了
Control, Maneuvering. We're losing electrical frequency.
声纳室叫指挥部 电力中斯
Control, Sonar. Total power supplies failure on all sets.
浮出水面
Surface! Blow forward! Blow aft!
准备潜望镜
Up scope. Stand by.
她在哪
Where the hell is she?
就在我们后面
She's right behind us.
不可能的
Impossible.
二号船坞准备
Stand by on number two dock.
尼帕鲁斯号船员们 各就各位
Liparus crew, take up positions.
船坞船员到操作室
Dock Officer to Operations.
调动组组员进入船坞范围
Mobilization crew entering dock area.
二号船坞呼叫操作室
Number two dock to Operations.
还有二十五米 我重复
Twenty-five meters to run. I say again.
操作室呼叫二号船坞 船只已进入船坞
Operation Room to number two dock. Docking now complete.
登陆船员各就各位
Disembarkation crew moving into position.
S射线程序完成 磁场关闭
S Ray program completed. Magnetic field shut down.
系统正常
All systems normal.
扬声器已准备好
Limpet speaker in position, sir.
司令官 你有两分钟的时间…
Commander, you have precisely two minutes...
打开舱口 弃船投降
to open your hatches and surrender your ship.
否则你们会被…氰毒气处决
The alternative is extermination by cyanide gas.
怎么办?
Well?
根本没有选择
There's no alternative.
你们听好船长的说话
Now hear this. Your Captain speaking.
把所有舱口打开 肃静的离开船只
Open all hatches and proceed quietly onto the casing.
赶快 我没什么耐性的
Hurry, Commander. I'm not renown for my patience.
列成两队 行动
Okay, two ranks. Move it out.
紧紧跟着我 我们会尽量掩护你
Stay close to me. We'll try and hide you.
时间有限
Our time is limited, Captain.
- 马上开始行动 - 遵命
- Commence operations forthwith. - Yes, sir.
所有人员听好
Attention all personnel.
斯特龙伯格第一及第二队
Stromberg crews One and Two...
要登上你们的潜艇
embark your submarines.
把这些美国人跟其他人关在一起
Put the Americans in with the others, Captain.
把俘虏带走
Remove the prisoners.
别抬头望 有人在偷拍我们
Don't look up. You're on Candid Camera.
已经装上核导弹
Complete nuclear missile loading.
雷达室呼叫操作室 方圆二万五千米以内没有联络
Operations, Radar. No contacts within 25,000 meters.
把那两名俘虏带进来
Bring those two prisoners here.
走吧
Let's go. Come on now.
声纳室叫操作室
Operations Room, Sonar.
不准联络和发送
No contacts, no transmissions.
停止稳定装置
Cease stable hold.
你们真是锲而不舍
You have certainly been persistent.
现在我可以满足你们的好奇心
Very well. Now your curiosity can be satisfied.
两组的人员已经登船
Both crews aboard, sir.
核导弹已经装置完毕
Missile onload completed.
他们已经知道了自己的目标
They have already been given their targets.
它们在十二点整低达开火的位置
At 12:00 noon, they will have reached firing positions.
纽约和莫斯科…
Within minutes, New York and Moscow...
很快就会消失
will cease to exist.
接着世界将会瓦解
Global destruction will follow.
新的纪元即将开始
The new era will begin.
一号及二号潜艇
Submarines One and Two...
开始出发程序
commence departure drill.
好 我知道你是来真的了
All right, you've made your point.
你想要多少?
How much do you want?
多少?
"How much?"
究竟你指的是什么?
Whatever do you mean, Mr. Bond?
不发射核导弹的代价
The price for not firing those nuclear missiles.
你受骗了
You're deluded, Mr. Bond.
我并不是要敲诈勒索
I'm not interested in extortion.
我只是要改变历史的面貌
I intend to change the face of history.
所以你要毁灭世界?
By destroying the world?
应该说是创造世界
By creating a world.
一个在海洋里的美丽新世界
A new and beautiful world beneath the sea.
今天的人类文明既腐败又堕落
Today, civilization as we know it is corrupt and decadent.
终有一天会自取灭亡
Inevitably, it will destroy itself.
我只是加速这件事的发生而已
I'm merely accelerating the process.
还并不能为大屠杀辩护
That does not justify mass murder.
对与错
For that, Major...
我会留待后世去评价
I will accept the judgment of posterity.
潜艇可以出发了
Submarines ready for departure, sir.
打开船头的门
Open bow doors, Captain.
斯特龙伯格一号
Stromberg One...
你可以出发
you are clear to proceed to sea.
斯特龙伯格二号 你也可以出发
Stromberg Two, you are also clear to proceed to sea. Forward stern.
好好看清楚用来毁灭世界的工具
Observe, Mr. Bond, the instruments of Armageddon.
把这个人跟其他俘虏一并关起来
Put this man with the rest of the prisoners.
还位小姐会跟我一起到亚特兰蒂斯去
The lady will be traveling to Atlantis with me.
别了 邦德先生
Farewell, Mr. Bond.
我得说 这个词语…
That word has, I must admit...
这次意味着永恒的离别
a welcome ring of permanency about it.
再见 安雅
Au revoir, Anya.
把她带走
Bring her.
抓着他
Get that man!
继续前进
Keep going.
你叫他过来
Call him over.
- 船长在哪? - 我就是
- Where's your captain? - Here.
去找其他人 然后到军械库
Release the other crews, then make for the armory.
跟我来 赶快
Follow me, men. At the double.
来 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
把操作室密封起来
Seal the operations room!
你到那里准备
You! Stand by over there!
拿武器
Help yourself to firearms!
拿武器 走
Grab a weapon. Come on, let's go.
我们已占领了船坞范围 但你们的船长已经死了
We've taken both sides of the lower dock area, but your captain's dead.
我们还是无法走近控制室
We're still no closer to that control room.
让我来吧
Leave it to me, sir.
安德鲁 詹姆斯 马歇尔 帕维斯跟我来
Andrews, James, Marchal, Purvis. Follow me.
那些铜板一定有几寸厚
That armored plating must be inches thick.
- 我们无法把它射穿的 - 到军械库去
- We'll never get through it. - Let's get to the armory.
- 你要到那里找什么 - 核导弹
- What do you reckon to find there? - A nuclear missile.
等等!
A nuc... Hey, wait!
这需要很长时间的
This could take hours, sir.
你有约会吗?
You got a date?
没有
No, sir.
你真漂亮
Now you are beautiful.
若你觉得很辛苦 很对不起
I'm sorry if you feel less than comfortable...
可是你有暴力倾向 我得把它控制
but you have a tendency to violence that must be controlled.
- 怎么了? - 我得报告
- What is it? - I have to report, sir...
有些犯人逃了
a breakout by some of the prisoners.
真是令人遗憾
That is unfortunate, Captain.
不过 情况已经受到控制了
However, sir, we now have the situation under control.
他们无法把控制室攻破
The operations room is quite impregnable.
希望你们不要再发生不幸的事故
Then we must hope, Captain, that you will suffer no further mishap.
我要把雷管取出来
All I need out of here is the detonator.
你真的知道自己在干吗?
James, are you sure you know what you're doing?
凡事总有第一次
There has to be a first time for everything.
可恶
Blast.
怎么了
What's the problem?
我不能碰到脉动导体电路的任何一部分
I mustn't touch any part of the impulse conductor circuit.
脉动导体电路就储藏在这里
This ring houses the impulse conductor circuit, sir.
它是有磁性的 雷管万万不能碰到它
It's magnetic. I mustn't touch it with any part of the detonator.
- 若碰到了会怎么样? - 它会爆炸
- What happens if you do? - It'll go off.
- 我要六号雷管 - 知道
- Get me a number six detonator. - Aye, aye, sir.
- 六号 - 谢谢
- Number six, sir. - Thank you.
你是否准备了二十秒的导火线吗?
Did you fix that 20-second fuse?
是的 在这里
Yes, sir. Here it is.
塑胶炸弹
Plastic explosive.
一切顺利吗?
Is everything proceeding according to plan?
- 顺利 - 好极了
- Yes, sir. - Excellent.
- 长官? - 怎么了?
- Sir? - What is it?
画面消失了
The monitors faded.
改变电路
Change the circuit.
停火
Cease fire!
已经太迟了
You're too late, Bond.
潜艇已经到达指定位置
Our submarines are already on station.
导弹将会于四分钟之后发射
In four minutes, the missiles will be launched.
你会操作电报装置吗?
Can you work the printout transmission unit?
会 但是我们只剩下三分钟
Sure, but we've only got three minutes.
只要我们找出潜艇的位置 就可以把程序改编
If we can work out the position of those submarines, maybe we can reprogram them.
- 干什么? - 让他们自相残杀
- To do what? - To destroy each other.
(位置及移动方向)
詹姆斯! 那圆球
James! The globe!
把一号潜艇的位置列为二号潜艇的目标
Pass the position of the first submarine to the second as their target.
- 反之亦然 - 没错
- And vice versa? - Exactly.
导弹控制室 我是船长 目标有变
Missile Control, this is the Captain. We have a change of target.
新的坐标是034285219
New coordinates are 034285219.
导弹控制室 我是船长 目标有变
Missile Control, Captain. We have a new target.
大家回到潜艇里去 传话
Everybody back on board the submarine! Pass it on!
快走
Come on! Let's go!
清除航线上的障碍 快
Foster, get those lines cleared! Come on!
大家让路
Leaver, throw those guys a line!
把前后的防护板清除
Get those block fenders cleared! Fore and aft!
把潜艇调整至下潜的状态
Get the submarine at diving stations!
驾驶舱呼叫指挥部 反应堆只剩下一半的动力
Control, Maneuvering. Reactor at half-power state.
可以接受电报
Ready to check telegraphs.
所有人员马上就位
All personnel, take up positions fast!
- 叫劳勃操作回转仪 - 好
- Get Roberts in the gyro unit. - Right.
快走
Come on! Move it!
准备恢复正常灯光
Stand by to revert to normal lighting.
赶快把舱门关上
Come on, sailor. Get that hatch shut quick.
- 指挥部呼叫鱼雷室 - 鱼雷室收到
- Torpedo Room, Control. - Torpedo Room.
把46号鱼雷装上一号管道
Load tube one with mark 46 torpedo.
把一号管道的外层出口打开
Open outer door on tube one.
回转仪角度为零度
Select zero gyro angle.
外层出口已经打开
Outer door on tube one open.
瞄准目标 发射
Match bearings and shoot.
- 准备 - 发射
- Set. - Shoot.
鱼雷已经发射
Torpedo running.
在船体中部装舵 在前头三分二的地方
Rudder amidships. Ahead two-thirds.
向左移7度
Left seven degrees rudder.
你认为有多远?
How far would you say?
- 大概是一万码 - 指挥官
- About 10,000 yards, sir. - Commander.
关门
Close it.
我收到国防部的讯号
I just got this signal from the Pentagon.
安全理事会发出指示
On instructions from the Security Council:
"从速把阿特兰蒂斯毁灭"
"Destroy Atlantis fast. "
从速是什么意思?
What does "fast" mean?
五分钟后进入作战状态
Battle stations five minutes.
发射鱼雷?
With torpedoes?
对
Yes.
可是安雅还在里面
He has Anya on there.
- 很抱歉 - 我要去救她
- I know. I'm sorry. - I have to get her off.
- 如何? -  可以把Q送来的装备给我吗?
- How? - Can I have the equipment Q sent?
好的
Sure.
马上把邦德中校的包裹送过来
Barton. That package for Commander Bond, bring it in quick.
- 给我一小时 - 那是最高指令
- I need an hour. - That comes from the top!
四十分钟
Forty minutes!
你可以把我交给军事法庭
You're gonna get me court-martialed.
一小时
One hour.
进来
Come in.
我帮你
I'll give you a hand.
晚上好 我正在恭候你大驾
Good evening, Mr. Bond. I've been expecting you.
你别动 会有升降机下来接你
Stay where you are. I'll send the elevator down for you.
再见了
Good-bye, Mr. Bond.
你真的想我掉下去
You did want me to drop in.
- 安雅在哪?  - 喔...
- Where's Anya? - Well, well, well.
英国特工爱上俄国特工
A British agent in love with a Russian agent.
想建立缓和关系吧
Detente, indeed.
请坐
Sit down, Mr. Bond.
- 你已经没有太多时间了 - 你也是
- Your time is running out. - Yours too, Mr. Bond.
比你想像中的还要快
And faster than you think.
你已经射了一箭 现在到我了
You shot your bolt. Now it's my turn.
(逃生舱)
你觉得如何?
How does that grab you?
已经超过了五分钟 船长
We're five minutes overdue, Captain.
- 斯特龙伯格在哪 - 他死了
- Stromberg? - Dead.
若还不快逃命 我们也会没命
So are we unless we get out of here fast.
瞄准目标 发射
Match bearings and shoot.
也许我低估了斯特龙伯格
Maybe I misjudged Stromberg.
会欣赏52年的香槟的人都不会是大坏蛋
Any man who drinks Dom Perignon '52 can't be all bad.
任务已经完成 指挥官
The mission is over, Commander.
我国的死囚可以有最后的请求
In my country, the condemned man is usually allowed a final request.
我批准
Granted.
我们把还些湿衣服脱下来吧
Let's get out of these wet things.
可是我们的上司会怎么想?
But, James, what would our superiors say?
他们不会知道的
They'll never know.
把船尾的闸门放下
Lower the stern gate.
- 他们会患上减压病吗?  - 很快就会知道
- Is there danger of the bends? - We'll soon find out.
- 邦德 - 3X
- 007. - XXX.
邦德 你在干吗?
What are you doing?
我是为了国家而做的
Keeping the British end up, sir.